packed with the
porches
Five
lame,
blind and the
pool.
one
all staring at
stirs,
When the water
in
the first one
only
healed.
is
whoever
rewards
A cure that
fastest.
is
there
lying
So the man
years
thirty-eight
be
ever
too weak to
first
chance.
stood a
never
crowd
walks past the
Jesus
man
one
and finds the
reach the
never
who could
water.
asks,
He
whole?"
made
"Wilt thou be
the
knows
The man only
answer:
old
before
steps down
always
someone
him.
skips the pool
Jesus
So
entirely:
"Rise,
bed,
take up thy
isn't
That question
walk."
and
a
strength from
demanding
Jesus
man.
weak
the false
exposing
It's grace
at for
you've stared
hope
years
close the
must
that you
before He
God
distance to
acts.
the water.
touched
He never
spoke
He
lost
who'd
and a man
years
thirty-eight
every race for
up.
stood
who
one
the
Christ reached
reach Him.
never
could